#### Contact

8500715871 (Home) abdulkhaleelshaik001@gmail. com

www.linkedin.com/in/abdulshaik12 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Data Analysis
Machine Learning
SQL

#### Certifications

Python for Data Science and Machine Learning Bootcamp

Deep Learning Essentials with Keras
Python

SQL

Applied Text Mining in Python

# **Abdul Khaleel Shaik**

Data Analyst at Cartesian Consulting
Guntur

# Summary

I worked as an Risk Investigator in amazon for 8 months. We used to handle seller account which had Ton of seller data on which we investigate(one of the prominent and learning aspect) and take actions which makes huge difference to the business. While working as we were handling lot of data i got to know what career i want to peruse in future which was Data Science.

# Experience

Cartesian Consulting
Data Analyst
March 2020 - Present (6 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka

We interpret data and turns it into information that can offer ways to improve a business, thus affecting business decisions. Data Analysts gather information from various databases and interpret patterns and trends.

#### Amazon

Transaction Risk Investigator
October 2018 - June 2019 (9 months)
Hyderabad Area, India

analyzing seller accounts.

Tech Mahindra Customer Service Representative January 2018 - June 2018 (6 months) Hyderabad Area, India

Worked as Customer Service Representative used to handle calls and back end work.

## Education

**Great Learning** 

Master's degree, Data Science · (2019 - 2019)

Lovely Professional University

Bachelor's degree, Mechanical Engineering · (2014 - 2017)